Killer instincts die hard.
Dangerous is a action, thriller film directed by David Hackl.
A reformed sociopath heads to a remote island after the death of his brother.
Soon after his arrival, the island falls under siege from a deadly gang of mercenaries, and when he
discovers their role in his brother’s demise, he sets out on a relentless quest for vengeance.
Dylan "D" Forrester, played by Scott Eastwood.
Dr. Alderwood, played by Mel Gibson.
Sheriff McCoy, played by Tyrese Gibson.
Cole, played by Kevin Durand.
Agent Shaughnessy, played by Famke Janssen.
Linda Forrester, played by Brenda Bazinet.
Dangerous is a 2021 action thriller film directed by David Hackl and starring Scott
Eastwood, Tyrese Gibson, Famke Janssen, Kevin Durand, and Mel Gibson.
The film was released on November 5, 2021.
It was David Hackl's fifth film as director.
Dangerous was produced by Kevin DeWalt, Ben DeWalt and Doug Falconer under the banners of Mind's Eye Entertainment and Falconer
Pictures; and marks the last film of Falconer as a producer - he suddenly died in July 2021 before the release of the film.
The film was distributed in the United States and
the United Kingdom by Lionsgate.
It received negative reviews from critics for its plot and action.
The tone is intense.